# **SEAN MILFORT**

System Administrator II



## Summary

System Administrator II with 6+ years of experience implementing new solutions and strategies in multiple organizations. Passion for development work and learning different languages for building side projects during free time. Currently working on a master's degree for Computer Information Science.

# **Work Experience**

## Rite Aid | Camp Hill, PA System Administrator II

Maintaining AirWatch MDM Environment for 10,000+ devices

September 2021 - Present

September 2021 - Present

- Developing/Testing New Technologies for Store Environment
- WellSpan Health | York, PA

## System Administrator

December 2019 - September 2021

December 2019 - September 2021

- Creating/Developing Application Packages & Software Installations for mass/minor deployments
- Creating Technical/Support Documentation for new & existing solutions
- Evaluating/Designing Technical Solutions to improve End User Workflow
- Developing/Troubleshooting Mobile Device Management Solutions (AirWatch)
- Maintaining/Improving IT Environment with new Technological Improvements

#### Burlington Stores, Inc. | Burlington, NJ

**April 2015 - November 2019** 

#### IT Integration Analyst II

November 2017 – November 2019

- Responsible for large-scale Engineering/Design changes to our Mobile Device Management Platform (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ devices (iOS, Android & Windows CE)
- Created Installer/Scripting Packages for silent installations for 15,000 Machine (Unix Scripting, PowerShell & Bash)
- Developed/Maintained the Base Computer Image for 4,000+ machines (Windows/Mac)
- Created/Edited/Deployed Group Policy 15,000+ active devices
- Evaluated/Met with Senior Business Partners/Vendors on multiple different initiatives

#### IT Integration Analyst I

April 2017 – November 2017

- Implemented/Led Microsoft Surface Project in Corporate/Field Environment
- Planned/Integrated New Technology into Current Environment
- Maintained/Deployed Bi-Quarterly Updates to 4,000+ Machines
- Handled Maintenance/Support/Upgrades of Mobile Device Management Product (AirWatch) containing 11,000+ active devices
- Researched/Suggested Solutions to improve Productivity/Performance

### **IT Integration Associate**

October 2016 - April 2017

Helped Create/Set the company standard for Corporate Level Devices (Windows/Mac)

- Created Mobile profiles and packages for iOS Devices in Corporate/Store Environment for 4,000+ Mobile Devices
- Authored/Maintained Support and Procedural Documentation for Support Teams
- Created/Deployed Software Packages on large scale for Endpoints (Windows/Mac)

## Client Technologies Technician I

April 2015 - October 2016

- Supported/Troubleshooted Windows and Mac Machines on a large scale
- Participated in many different with various projects with different departments in IT
- Supported Mobile Devices (iPad and iPhones) while utilizing AirWatch as MDM tool
- Basic Network troubleshooting and configuration (DNS, VLAN, Connectivity)
- Delivered Customer Service to Troubleshoot and Enhance End User Experience

## **Skills**

**Languages** JavaScript

HTML & CSS PowerShell Bash Scripting

#### **Infrastructure Skills**

OS Management (Windows, macOS, Android, Linux & iOS)
Mobile Device Management
Active Directory & Group Policy Management
Large Scale Packaging & Deployment
Microsoft Deployment Toolkit

#### **Interpersonal Skills**

Leadership
Teamwork
Technical Documentation
Customer Service
Communication

## **Awards**

#### **CIO Award**

Dennis Hodgson, CIO, Burlington Stores, Inc. *April 2018* 

#### **CEO Award**

Thomas Kingsbury, CEO, Burlington Stores, Inc. *September 2017* 

## Education

La Salle University, Expected Graduation in 2022
Master of Science (M.S.), Computer Information Science

Philadelphia, PA

La Salle University, 2015
Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Computer Science

Philadelphia, PA